(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T10:02:05.187794",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
本日は！
Thank you so much...
角巻わためセカンドライブ
わためぇNight Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATERに
for attending Tsunomaki Watame's 2nd Live,
"Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER"!
ご来場いただきまして、
まことにありがとうございます！
Thank you so very much!
開演に先立ちまして、
お客様にご注意並びにご案内申し上げます。
Before the show begins, we would like to
make a few important notices and announcements.
公演中の撮影・録音・録画機材の使用は
硬くお断り致します。
The use of recording, filming, or photography
equipment during the concert is strictly prohibited.
会場内でのモッシュ・ダイブ・肩車、
Mosh pits, diving, sitting on shoulders,
ステージ上に物を投げ込む、
throwing objects onto the stage,
ステージ上に上がる、
climbing onto the stage,
故意に通路を塞ぐ、前に押し寄せる、
intentionally blocking aisles, or rushing forward,
周りのお客さまのご迷惑となるような
不自然なコール・奇声、
unnatural calls or strange noises that disturb
those around you,
公演の妨げとなるような
大きな音を鳴らす等の行為、
making loud noises that disrupt the performance,
不自然なタイミングで
両手を左右に激しく振る、
violently waving both hands left and right at unnatural times,
腕を振り回す・上半身をそらす…等の
flailing arms, arching the upper body,
過激な応援行為、過激なジャンプ行為…等、
and other extreme cheering or jumping behaviors
他のお客さまのご迷惑になる
または公演を妨げる危険行為は一切禁止です。
that disturb others or disrupt the show are strictly banned.
本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
客席のお客さまの様子が映り込む場合がございます。
Please note that video and photo cameras will be operating in the venue,
and audience members may be captured in the footage.
これら映像や写真はプロモーション等に
使用される可能性がございますので予めご了承下さい。
This footage and photographs may be used for promotional purposes,
so your understanding is appreciated in advance.
万が一、体調に異変を感じる場合は
無理をせず係員へお申し出ください。
If you feel unwell at any time, please do not push yourself
and notify a staff member immediately.
それでは！まもなく開演いたします！
And now, the show will begin shortly!
お席に着いてお待ち下さい！
Please take your seats and wait!
以上、角巻わためでした！
That is all from Tsunomaki Watame!
推しの曲 めっちゃいいね！
"Your favorite artist's song is so good!"
みるハコチャンス！
"Miruhako Chance!"
こんばんドドド！
Good evening-dodo!
みるハコ by JOYSOUND
Miruhako by JOYSOUND
こんばんドドド！
Good evening-dodo!
角巻ニュースのお時間です
It's time for Tsunomaki News.
It's time for Tsunomaki News!
いよいよ始まる!!
It's finally starting!!
角巻わためセカンドライブ わためぇ Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATERで
At Tsunomaki Watame's 2nd Live, "Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER,"
販売しているグッズ紹介をしたいと思います!
I'd like to introduce the merchandise on sale!
まずは…こちら～!!
First up... is this~!!
「わためいとらいとーーはっ」
The "Watameito Lighta~!"
わためいとの形になっているペンライト!
A penlight shaped like a Watameito!
みんなで左右に振ったり同じ色で揃えてみたり、
Waving them side to side together or matching colors,
会場のみんなも配信で観ているみんも一体になれる素敵なアイテムです!
it's a wonderful item that brings everyone in the venue and stream together!
次に紹介するのは…こちら! 「アクリルペンライトスタンド」&「タペストリー」!
Next up... are these! The "Acrylic Penlight Stand" & "Tapestry"!
こちらがなんとペンライトと一緒に飾ることが出来るアクリルスタンドになっています!
These are acrylic stands that let you display them right alongside your penlight!
タペストリーや他のライブグッズと一緒に並べて飾ってくださ～い!
Please display them alongside the tapestry and other live merchandise!
まだまだあるよ～! 次はこちら!
There's still more~! Next is this!
「マフラータオル」!
The "Muffler Towel"!
ライブで流した汗を拭いたり掲げたりいろんな使い方が…
You can use it in all sorts of ways, like wiping away sweat or holding it up at the live...
いろんな使い方ができる定番アイテムです!
It's a staple item with endless uses!
周りに気をつけながらタオルを振り回してもOKですよ～!
It's totally fine to swing the towel around, just watch out for those around you~!
どんどん行きましょう! 次は…こちら!
Let's keep rolling! Next is... this!
「わためのおもしろなりきりサングラス」!
Watame's "Funny Cosplay Sunglasses"!
これをかけたらみんなもわためになれちゃうかも?
Put these on and maybe you can become Watame too?
みんなでサングラスをかけて角巻わためになりきろう!
Put on the sunglasses together and let's become Tsunomaki Watame!
みんなついてきてますか? 大丈夫ですか?
Is everyone keeping up? Are you doing okay?
お次は…行きますよ! こちら!
Next up... here we go! This!
「エア・ギターTシャツ」!
The "Air Guitar T-Shirt"!
その名の通り、なんとエア・ギターが出来ちゃうTシャツなんですねえ!
Just as the name implies, it's a T-shirt that actually lets you play air guitar!
わためも実はちょっとエア・ギターを練習中!
Watame is actually practicing air guitar a bit too!
曲に合わせて一緒にかき鳴らそう～!
Let's strum along together to the music~!
これで終わりじゃありません! 次のグッズはこちら!
This isn't the end yet! The next merchandise is this!
「もこもこキャップ」! かわいい!
The "Fluffy Cap"! So cute!
羊をイメージして作ったカジュアルなキャップです!
It's a casual cap designed with sheep in mind!
ライブだけでなく普段でも使えるおしゃれなアイテム!
A stylish item you can wear not just at the live, but every day!
ラストスパート行きますよ～! お次は…こちら!
Entering the final stretch~! Next is... this!
「ラバーコースター」! ギターピックの形になっているので、
The "Rubber Coaster"! Shaped like a guitar pick,
これでギターを弾くも良し飾るも良し飲み物の下に敷くも良し!
you can play guitar with it, display it, or put your drink on it!
そして…最後のグッズはこれだ～!!
And... the final merchandise is this~!
「セトリキーホルダー」!
The "Setlist Keychain"!
今日のライブのセットリストがキーホルダーになります!
Today's live setlist becomes a keychain!
ライブであんな曲やこんな曲やってたな～って思い出してくれたら嬉しいです!
I'd be so happy if this helps you remember all the songs we played at the live!
詳しくは公演サイトと販売サイトチェックしてみてね～!
Be sure to check the performance and merch sites for details~!
以上、角巻わためより2ndライブグッズ紹介をお送りしました～!
That's all for Tsunomaki Watame's 2nd live merchandise introduction~!
いつだって そう 「僕 なんて」 ってさ
Always thinking, "Not me..."
俯いていた ばかり の may day
On just another dejected may day.
つまづいて 泣いて 「どうせ」 って口癖が染みついてさ
Tripping, crying, with "whatever" as a habit,
いつからかまた 積もる 焦り
impatience started piling up once again.
でも 胸 の 奥 に ある 光
But deep within my chest, a light shines on,
繋ぐ 点 と 線 の 上
connecting dots upon a line.
踏み出す イメージ の 先 へ
Stepping beyond my imagination's edge.
遠く たって いい
It's okay if it's far away,
ほら 虹 を またい で
look, stepping right across the rainbow.
さあ 心 の まま に 音 を 奏でる
Now, let's play the music straight from the heart.
逸る 鼓動 は 今 を 刻む 証 だ
This racing pulse is proof of the present moment.
響け 僕ら の 想い を 乗せ て
Resound, carrying our feelings within,
高く 遠く 歌 を 紡いで
spinning a song high and far away.
la la la
季節 巡っ て 駆け抜け て
Seasons revolve as we run right through,
気づけ ば 大人 に なっ て
before I knew it, I became an adult.
幼い 日 の 心 は 胸 の 奥くすぶっ て た
My childhood heart was smoldering deep inside.
怖い こと も 増え た けど
Things to fear have only grown,
でも 今 だ から 見える 世界
but this world is only visible right now.
僅か の 中 に 確実 に 灯る 光
A small yet certain light flickers brightly,
繋いで いこ う
so let's keep it connected.
さあ 新しい ステージ へ
Now, onto a brand new stage,
心 の 中 の 音 を 聴か せ て
let me hear the music inside your heart.
大袈裟 だって いい
It's okay to make a big deal out of it,
ありのまま の 自分 で
just being your true self.
咲き 誇れ もっと
Bloom even more proudly,
いつまで も ずっと
forever and ever,
歌い ながら 日々 を 紡いで
spinning each day while singing along.
俯い て 泣い た 日 も あっ た
There were days I hung my head and cried,
だけど 涙 も 力 に なる
but even tears become my strength.
本日は「角巻わため 2nd Live わためえNight Fever!!
Thank you very much for attending today's Tsunomaki Watame 2nd Live
in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER」にご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Watame Night Fever!! in TOKYO GARDEN THEATER.
開演に先立ちまして、
Before the concert begins,
お客さまにご注意ならびにご案内申しあげます。
we would like to make a few announcements and reminders.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機器の使用は
The use of photography, recording, and filming equipment during the show
かたくお断りいたします。
strictly prohibited.
場内は禁煙となっております。
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue.
喫煙はご遠慮くださいますようお願い申し上げます。
Please refrain from smoking anywhere on the premises.
万が一、体調に異変を感じる場合は、無理をせず係員へお申し出ください。
If you feel unwell at any time, please do not push yourself and notify a staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、肩車、
Mosh pits, stage diving, shoulder-riding,
ステージ上に物を投げ込む、
throwing objects onto the stage,
ステージ上に上がる、声援に通路を塞ぐ、
getting onto the stage, blocking aisles with cheers,
前に押し寄せるなど、周りのお客さまのご迷惑となるような不遜なコール、規制、
surging forward, and other disruptive behaviors that inconvenience surrounding guests,
公演の妨げとなる大きな音を鳴らす等の行為、
making loud noises that interfere with the performance,
不自然なタイミングで両手を左右に激しく振る、
violently swinging arms left and right at unnatural timings,
腕を振り回す、上半身をそらすなどの過激な応援行為、
swinging arms around, arching the upper body,
過度なジャンプ行為等、他の客さまのご迷惑となる、公演を妨げる危険行為は一切禁止です。
excessive jumping, and other dangerous or disruptive actions are strictly prohibited.
係員の指示及び注意に従わずに生じた事故や機材破損、
Accidents or equipment damage caused by failing to follow staff instructions,
トラブルについて、主催者、出演者、関係各人は一切の責任を負いかねます。
The organizers, performers, and related parties assume no responsibility for such trouble.
また、上記指示、注意を無視して生じた機材破損やトラブル等における損害賠償は、
Please also be aware that compensation for damages resulting from ignoring these instructions
加害者の責任となりますことをあらかじめご了解ください。
will be the responsibility of the perpetrator.
本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
Please note that video streaming and photography cameras will enter the venue,
客席のお客さまの様子が映り込む場合がございます。
and audience members may appear in the footage.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
These images and photographs may be used for promotional purposes, so please understand this in advance.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Thank you for your patience. Please wait a moment until the show begins.
オレの名前を言ってみろ！
Say my name!
今日は最高に楽しんでいきましょう！
Let's have the best time today!
もうちょっと待ってくれ！
Wait just a little longer!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
わだめぇナイトフィーバー！
Watame Night Fever!
弾けるリズムに合わせて
In time to the pounding rhythm,
嫌なこと全部忘れて
forget all your troubles!
みんなもっと声出せるよね！
Everyone can raise your voices more!
みんなの声聞かせて！
Let me hear everyone's voices!
ありがとう！もっと踊って！
Thank you! Keep dancing!
みんなもっと寂しいもんなの？
Are you all missing me that much?
意外と甘えん坊だな
You're surprisingly spoiled,
意外とおてんばじゃん
and surprisingly tomboyish too.
意外と照れ屋だね
Surprisingly shy,
丸い飛行雲 飛び出した彼女に
saying goodbye to the girl who flew out
さようなら
in round contrails.
ささやかなコンディショナー
A modest conditioner,
余るほどのスパイス
more than enough spice,
浮かぶ夢見てごこち
floating, dreaming comfortably.
あまるはすぐ水ぶき
Wiping up the excess right away,
ふわふわふかぶか
Fluffy and deep,
浮かぶ夢見心地
floating and dreaming comfortably.
一つ一つ数えて
Counting one by one,
おやすみなさい
go to sleep.
密かに目覚めた
This feeling
この気持ち
that quietly awakened,
まっすぐ見つめないで
don't stare straight at me.
まっすぐ見つめられたら
If you look straight at me,
なんちゃって そんな君が好きじゃん
Just kidding, I love that kind of you, right?
手探りじゃちゃらけちゃダメじゃん
Fooling around blindly won't do, right?
本当の本当は隠したいんじゃないの？
Don't you want to hide the honest truth?
もっとじゃないの 乗りが曖昧じゃないの
Isn't there more? Isn't the vibe a bit vague?
この気持ちはまちがいじゃないの
Isn't this feeling a mistake?
指切りげんまん
Pinky swear,
かなり閉じこで
locked up tightly,
優柔不断でもさ
even if you're indecisive,
絶対に毎日に
you'll definitely find
愛に来てくれるよね？
someone coming to love you every day, right?
満開臆病で
In full bloom, cowardly,
おんなじ気持ちで
with the same feeling,
全然変わらずに
without changing at all,
君にばっか あたりまえのように
always focusing on you as if it's only natural.
チャン×チャン
Chance x Chance
逢！！チキチキバンバン
Meet!! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
哀！？チキチキ チャン チャン
Sorrow!? Chitty Chitty Chance Chance
嗚呼！チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
愛！！チョキチョキチョキ バンバン
Love!! Choki Choki Choki Bang Bang
猫も杓子も みんないきれいで 辛い
Everyone is fickle and it's tough,
酔えば テキーラ あらぬ妄想
getting drunk on tequila, crazy delusions
連続で ピーカーン
flashing one after another.
夢は パンドラ ほら 開きたくなるの
Dreams are Pandora's box, open it up!
みんな 期待して パリピ よ
Everyone is expecting it, party people.
今夜 フジヤマ 登る にゃ 分からない
Tonight we climb Mt. Fuji, who knows?
決戦 も 週末 の 宿命
The decisive battle is weekend's fate.
チャン×チャン
Chance x Chance
逢！！チキチキバンバン
Meet!! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
何も勿体ぶらず 楽しめ フィーバー トゥナイト
Don't hold back, enjoy the fever tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance x Chance
哀！？チキチキ バンバン
Sorrow!? Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
何度ムシャクシャしたって パーリー トゥナイト
No matter how frustrated, party tonight!
チャン×チャン
Chance x Chance
嗚呼！チキチキバンバン
Ah! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
愚か者ほど high と化す 完全 社会
Fools get high in this perfect society.
チャン×チャン
Chance x Chance
愛！！チキチキバンバン
Love!! Chitty Chitty Bang Bang
みんなスーパースターの卵さ ディーヴァ トゥナイト
Budding superstars and divas tonight!
約束だぞ？
It's a promise, okay?
いっちゃった
Gone away...
もしかしたら 運命 とも
Perhaps even destiny...
言い切れない のかも
We can't say for sure.
いっちゃったかも
Maybe we've gone too far...
殆どのことが ばれてる のかも
Or maybe everything's exposed.
目覚められないかも
Maybe we can't wake up.
あいまいな世界じゃ
In this ambiguous world...
探して 私を見つけて
Search for me and find me.
すれ違い 波を掴むの上
Catching the waves of passing by...
ずるずる もつれた 歌詞の上
Over tangled, messy lyrics.
ドドドドド ドライブして
Driving on and on...
ギギギギ ギア入れて
Shifting gears!
パパパパ 片付けて
Tidying everything up!
さあ とびましょ
Come on, let's fly away!
音鳴らせ もっと もっと
Make the sound ring, more and more!
先々は ずっと ずっと
The future goes on and on!
今すぐたいへん 飛び込んでけ
Dive straight into the tough times right now!
ドドドドド ダンスしたら どんちゃんて
Dancing around with a big commotion,
ラララ ランシンソーになたって
lost in a frenzy of thoughts.
ミステリー ベス レジ って
Stretching past the mysteries,
どどどど どんちゃんて
with a big commotion!
けけけけ けっパ進むじゃんで
Pushing forward through the edges,
溜まって可能性 感じちゃって
feeling the piling possibilities,
つまり ナウを生きて
living right in the now!
すれ違い 散々 ビートの上
Passing by amidst the scattered beats...
それぞれ 散らかしてく この場で
Scattering things around in this place.
すすすす スライドして
Sliding smoothly on and on...
つつつつ つなぎいて
Linking it all together.
ここここ こんばんは
Hello to everyone here!
さあ とびましょ
Come on, let's fly away!
音鳴らせ もっと もっと
Make the sound ring, more and more!
神様は ごっと ごっと
God is great and amazing!
楽しみたい なら
If you want to have fun,
クロウは えちょこ
follow the rules right away.
どどどど ダンスしたら どんちゃんて
Dancing around with a big commotion,
ラララ ランシンソーになたって
lost in a frenzy of thoughts.
mayday, mayday
mayday 声は届いてる？
Mayday, are my words reaching you?
心がズキッと痛いみたい
It feels like my heart aches sharply.
baby なんて魅力的
Baby, how charming,
見せるテクニックはすぐにクラクラ
The techniques you show make me dizzy instantly.
mayday それじゃ物足りない
Mayday, that's not enough.
すぐにもっともっと欲張るスタイル
A greedy style asking for more and more right away.
hey-hey もっと焦がしてよ
Hey-hey, make me burn more.
あなたの心に入っていたいのにな
Even though I want to be inside your heart.
ah 見え透いた甘い罠
Ah, a transparent, sweet trap.
ah ハマってあげようか
Ah, shall I fall for it?
ah 自在にコントロールしていたはずなのにさ
Even though I should have been controlling it freely.
クラクラって酔いしれそうな
Dizzy, as if about to get intoxicated,
甘い匂い誘われ
Lured by a sweet scent.
フラフラって寄ってしまうわ
Tottering, I end up drawing close.
ああ もう help me
Ah, already, help me.
逃げたいわけじゃなくて
It's not that I want to run away,
これくらいがちょうどいいわなんてさ
Saying this much is just right.
もうキミの前じゃ絶対
Already, in front of you, absolutely,
help me して
Please help me.
mayday 舵が取れないの
Mayday, I can't steer.
気持ちがモヤッてハレないし
My feelings are hazy and won't clear up.
lady なんかじゃいられない
I can't stay a lady like this.
今時の girl はもうチョメチョメチョメ
A modern girl is already chome-chome.
絶対あるわけないじゃん
There's no way that's true.
絶対にただの勘違い
Definitely just a misunderstanding.
論外 手の平の上で踊らされているこの感じ
Being danced in the palm of your hand.
だってもう溶け出しそうな
Because it feels like I'm already melting,
体温に魅惑れ
Enchanted by my body temperature.
なんか変 あたしじゃないみたい
Something's weird, not like myself at all.
ああ もう rescue me
Ah, already, rescue me.
嫌々って漏れ出しちゃうくらいに
To the extent that reluctance leaks out,
あたしを困らせてなんだ
Teasing me and making me troubled.
もうあたしからは絶対
Already, from me, absolutely,
rescue me して
Please rescue me.
ねえどうして愛は悪戯するんだろう
Hey, why does love play tricks?
ねえいつかはこの痛みも消えるの
Hey, will this pain eventually disappear too?
本来は案外簡単に否定して壊れちゃうけど
Originally, it's quite easily denied and broken, but
傷だらけの心は
A scarred heart...
気付けば手を伸ばしちゃって
Before I knew it, I reached out my hand.
その遠さ苦しくて
That distance is painful.
キミも手を伸ばしてくれたなら
If you also reached out your hand,
イタイ ここにいたいのに
It hurts, even though I want to stay here.
cry 落ち着く場所
Cry, a place to calm down.
その手で触れてよほら mayday
Touch me with those hands, come on, mayday.
クラクラって酔いしれそうな
Dizzy, as if about to get intoxicated,
甘い匂い誘われ
Lured by a sweet scent.
フラフラって寄ってしまうわ
Tottering, I end up drawing close.
ああ もう save me
Ah, already, save me.
help me
rescue me
save me
mayday
Mayday, don't rescue me tonight.
だってもう溶け出しそうな
Because it feels like I'm already melting,
体温に魅惑れ
Enchanted by my body temperature.
きっとそう溢れだしたんだ
I'm sure it overflowed.
もう rescue me して
Already, please rescue me.
それまでの過ちも
Even the mistakes up until then
しょうがないけど歩みを進める
Can't be helped, but I keep moving forward.
振り返ることも時もあるけど
Sometimes I look back too,
それはほどほどでもいいよね
That's fine in moderation, right?
わかるなんて言葉はいつも
Words like "I understand" are always
聞き集めただけだけど信じていたい
Just gathered things, but I want to believe.
なんとか慣れなんとかでもあれもうさ
Somehow getting used to it, managing, come on.
強気な気持ちで光れ
Shine with a strong-willed feeling.
いつだってその瞳輝きを
Whenever it is, those eyes shine.
失うまでは光れそのまま構わない
Shine until you lose it, it's fine just like that.
いつか輝ける日が来るさ
A day will come when you can shine.
その瞳輝きを 失うまでは
Until those eyes lose their sparkle,
光れ そのままで構わない
Shine, it's fine just like that.
いつか輝ける日が来るさ
A day will come when you can shine.
時もたまにある燃え尽きることでではなくて
Sometimes it's not about burning out,
何がある揺れ動く感情答えなんてものは無いけど
Wavering emotions, though there's no answer.
キミが触れたその感触は君だけにしか確かめられないよ
What you touched can only be verified by you.
悔しい言葉バネにできないそんな時もあるよね
Times when frustrating words can't be a spring.
開け心の中の扉少しずつ飛んで抜け出して
Open your heart's door and fly away.
開け時間はかかるけれどいつか開けられる
It takes time, but it can be opened.
光が来るさ いつか開けられる
Light will come, it can be opened.
きっと
Surely...
心の中の扉少しずつ飛んで抜け出して
Open the door inside your heart, flying away.
開け時間はかかるけれどいつか開けられる
It takes time, but it can be opened.
光が来るさ いつか開けられる
Light will come, it can be opened.
いつか
Someday...
手を 手に入れて
Taking it in your hands...
いつか 聞いた
I heard it someday.
あのフレーズを
That phrase...
いつか 思い描いた星を
The stars I once dreamed of...
いつか 遠く で 叫ん で みる
Someday, I'll shout out into the distance.
Someday, I'll shout out into the distance,
きっと
for sure.
つのまきわため
Tsunomaki Watame's...
セカンドライブ！
Second Live!
わためナイトフィーバーに来てくれて、ありがとう！
Thank you for coming to Watame Night Fever!
緊張するわ…
I'm so nervous...
いやーみんなの声聞こえるよー！
Man, I can hear everyone's voices!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いや、震えあがってるよ、ガーデンシアターが。
Man, Garden Theater is shaking.
本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
ファーストからね、約2年ぶりということで。
It's been about two years since our first one.
ファーストも来た人いる？ あ、結構いる！
Anyone here who came to the first one? Oh, quite a few!
今日が初めての人…！ あ、結構いる！
People here for the first time...? Oh, quite a lot!
いやあ嬉しいね、いっぱい来てくれてありがとうございます。
I'm so happy, thank you all for coming out.
ねえみんな、新しいアルバムは聴いてくれた？
Hey everyone, did you listen to the new album?
すごいみんな聴いてくれてる！ ありがとうございます。
Wow, everyone listened to it! Thank you so much.
いや楽しいね！
Man, this is so fun!
今回はね、楽しいね！
This time... it's so fun!
今回はドドドバンドによる生演奏でのライブとなっておりまーす！
This live is performed live with the Dododo Band!
みんなね、素敵なバンドメンバーなんだけど、紹介してもいいですか？
They're all wonderful band members, can I introduce them?
ありがとう、ちょっとやってみたかったんだよこれ。嬉しいよ。じゃあやらせていただきます。
Thank you, I've kind of wanted to do that. I'm so happy. Well then, I'll go ahead.
On Bass! 朝ちゃんこと、朝倉高貴ー！
On Bass! Asachan, Takaki Asakura!
すごい朝ちゃーん！ すごいね、みんな優しいね。ありがとうございます。まだまだいるからね。
Amazing, Asachan! That's amazing, everyone is so kind. Thank you. There's still more, you know.
うん？ ドーラ、むーん？ 拓ちゃんこと、西澤拓真ー！
Hmm? Dora, moon? Takuchan, Takumi Nishizawa!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
そして、On Keyboard! たつんだ、じゃあ…
And, On Keyboard! Tatsun, then...
引くんだ、じゃあ… キーボード引けー！
Play it then... Play that keyboard!
とってもパリピな情です。盛り上がってるよ！ ありがとう。そして、
Such a party-people vibe. It's getting hyped! Thank you. And,
On Guitar and Band Masterを務めていただいております、オッケイはんこと？ 飯田ケイスケー！
On Guitar and Band Master, serving as our OK-han? Keisuke Iida!
On ボーカル！
On Vocals!
角巻わためー！
Tsunomaki Watame!
嬉しい！ 羊もいるな。声でかい羊がいるな。
I'm so happy! There's a sheep too. There's a loud sheep.
こちらのドドドバンドと一緒に今年は盛り上げていきたいと思います！
We're going to hype things up today together with the Dododo Band!
でもさ、みんなもメンバーじゃない？ ねえ？
But hey, aren't you guys members too? Right?
ちょっとコールアンドレスポンスやっていい？ いいー！
Can we do a call and response? Yeah!
じゃあまずいるかな？ 女の子！ イエーイ！
So first, are there... girls? Yeah!
なんか、あ、でも聞こえる！ 女の子だー！
Wait, oh, but I can hear them! Girls!
すごいすごい、ありがとう！うれしい！
Amazing, amazing, thank you! I'm so happy!
しきぴ、ありがとう！
Shikipi, thank you!
あたたかなかー！
So warm!
うわ、すごい！すげえぜ！
Whoa, amazing! This is incredible!
声でか！
Your voices are so loud!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
あたたかなかー、しきぴ！
So warm, Shikipi!
ありがとう！じゃあ、全員聞かせてくれ！イエーイ！
Thank you! Now, let everyone hear you! Yeah!
すごいな！気持ちいい！
This is amazing! It feels so good!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
もちろん、配信組のみんなの番もあるよ！
Of course, it's also time for everyone watching the stream!
配信組のみんなーー！
Everyone watching the streamーー!
イエーイ、コメント見えてますよ！
Yeah, I can see your comments!
ね、景色いいなって言ってる人いるわ！
Right, some people are saying the scenery is nice!
ね、ありがとう！
Right, thank you!
はい、ちょっとやりたいことまだある！ペンライトウェーブ！
Okay, there's something else I want to do! Penlight wave!
ペンライト持ってますか？
Do you have your penlights?
いや、みんな持ってるな！ありがとうございます！
Oh, you all have them! Thank you very much!
ファーストの時にやったウェーブやっていいですか？
Can we do the wave we did during the first [live]?
こっからいきますよ！
We'll start from over here!
いくよ！
Here we go!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
ついてこれてる？
Are you keeping up?
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
ついてこれてない？
Can't keep up?
大丈夫かな？
Are you alright?
いや、楽しいね！
Man, this is fun!
最高だ！
This is the best!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いや、今日はね、なんと韓国でもライブビューイングをしておりまして！
And today, amazingly, we're also having a live viewing in Korea!
韓国のみんな、アンニョンハセヨー！
Everyone in Korea, annyeonghaseyo!
カムサハムニダ！ありがとうございます！
Kamsahamnida! Thank you very much!
今日はね、ライブの感想をハッシュタグ「#角巻わため2ndライブ」でたくさんポストしてください！イエーイ！
Today, please post plenty of your live reviews with the hashtag '#TsunomakiWatame2ndLive'! Yeah!
今日はね、みんなと一緒に作り上げるライブだと思っているので！
Since I think this is a live show we're creating together with everyone,
ペンライト振ったり、タオル回したり、ギター弾いたりしたいって思っております！
I want us to wave our penlights, spin towels, and air-guitar!
できますか？
Can you do it?
できそうだね！
Sounds like you can!
頼むよ！そして、ステージに表示されるコール、歌詞、一緒に歌ってください！イエーイ！
I'm counting on you! And please sing along with the calls and lyrics displayed on stage! Yeah!
お願いしまーす！イエーイ！
Please do! Yeah!
なんとここで悲報です！
And now for some unfortunate news!
YouTube、TikTokでご覧の方はここまでとなります！えー！
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, this is where we part ways! Eh?!
みんな一緒に最後までいたいよね！ね、一緒に盛り上がりたいよね！
Everyone wants to stay together until the very end, right? Right, you want to get hyped together to the end!
概要欄から配信サイトへチケットを購入いただいて、最後まで一緒にいようよ！よろしくお願いします！イエーイ！
Please purchase a ticket to the streaming site from the description and let's stay together until the end! Thank you! Yeah!
ね、買ってねって！
Right, buy one!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
今回はね、いっぱいちょっと曲用意してきたから、早速次の曲にいきたいと思います！イエーイ！
Since I prepared plenty of songs this time, I'd like to move right on to the next song! Yeah!
次の曲もニューアルバムから！バンドの皆さん、演奏よろしくお願いします！イエーイ！
The next song is also from the new album! Band members, please start playing! Yeah!
無料パートは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!